<resources>
    <string name="app_name">#Quest-2017</string>
    <string name="e_mail">quest.cse@jntuh.ac.in</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Quest 2017</string>
    <string-array name="item_names">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Workshops</item>
        <item>Events</item>
        <item>Contact Us</item>
        <item>Get Directions</item>
        <item>Developer Credits</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="quote">"Debug Urself"</string>
    <string name="website"><u>www.csequest.com</u></string>
    <string name="jntuSite"><u>www.jntuhceh.ac.in</u></string>
    <string name="open">OPEN</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="description">Voila! The most excitedly awaited National level Gabfest, Quest is back after an year long halt with the most appealing loads of intriguing Events (Coding, Presentations , And many On-Spot events),Workshops and  other technical stuff.Witness the fest by taking part in various flashy activities and upgrade your knowledge.</string>
    <string name="jntuDesc">Situated at the heart of Hyderabad,Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University College of Engineering(Autonomous)
			has been providing top notch education to students since 1965.
			The infrastructure development in the past two decades in the college has been prominent.
			An accredited, comprehensive college, JNTUH CEH offers active learning in a vibrant atmosphere where students connect the classroom and their world.
			With a focus on innovative ideas along with curricular education. The nurturing environment offers
			education combined with practical experiences such as internships, academic and career counseling and volunteer opportunities.
			To meet the essential requirements for strengthening theutility of its programs, the college has developed its own
			infrastructure and services of the high quality, novel thoughts and practical approach. With the cooperation of the
			Faculty and other staff members, the institution is now capable to impart quality education for more than thousands
			students per year. At JNTUH CEH, we believe in making our students ready for the future,today.</string>
    <string name="prevspon"><u>Previous Sponsors :</u></string>
    <string name="qdescription">Ever since its inception, Quest has made a name for itself as an avant-garde technical festival, showcasing innovations in thefields of science and technology.
			With this two day long event, we bring to you a conglomerate of unique ideas,
			competent skill and unlimited fun. Through its plethora of competitions, lectures and workshops, Quest strives
			to ignite the minds of the students visiting the festival.From challenging the coder in you at all the coding events
			to bringing out the scholar in you at Paper presentations, the events are designed to tech-train young minds. We,
			the student community at Computer Science Department of JNTUH invite you to celebrate mutual passion and common
			thirst for knowledge. Meet like minded tech lovers and think beyond normal.Be a part of Quest and experience
			the ardour, for this is an event that truly justifies its name. And this time, its going to be the best ever.</string>
    <string name="about_quest">About QUEST</string>
</resources>
